Guide to the Ithaca Rotary Club Records, 1914-2016.
Ithaca Rotary Club Records
- Series IV. Secretaries
  - Oliver “Ollie” Jones, 1946-1966
    - John Van Cott, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Gov's Letters, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Members (Clippings), 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - International Office, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Material for Board, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Student Exchange, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Blank Roster Forms (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Frank R. Bliss, 1963-1964 and 1966-1970
    Bliss became secretary while Ollie Jones was District Governor, leaving the post on Jones’ return, and resuming it in 1966. He died while still secretary of the club in 1970.
    - Treasurer, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Year-end Reports, Rotary Club Committees, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Student Exchange, 1964-1966 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Attendance, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Rotary International, January 1966-July 1966 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Bulletin (Page 2) Material, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Misc. Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - District 717--R.I., 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - R.I. District 717, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Committee Chairmen., 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Memberships--Process, 1964-1966 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Board of Directors, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Rotary Foundation, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Pres. John Seeley, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Treasurer, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Rotary Foundation, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Secretary Correspondence, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Pres. Rob Polson, 1965-1966. (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Rotary International, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Bulletin Page 2, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Secretary's Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Committees, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - President Cole, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Sec's Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Rotary Committees, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Committees, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - International Service, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Members in the News, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Dist Governor, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Bulletins Page 2, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Student Exchange, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Treasurer, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Members--Correspondence With, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Available Speakers, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Rotary International, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Rotary International, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Oliver Jones, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Committee Chairmen., 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - FRB Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Directors--Board Meetings, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Treasurer--Fogelsanger, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Classifications Chairman, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Board of Directors, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - (Honorary) Members, 1963-1967 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Members Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Rotary Committees Final, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Bulletins, July 1968-July 1969 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - A. Makedon, Exchange, 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - "J--Student Exchange", 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Robert H. “Bob” Head, 1971-1980
    Bob Head’s files comprise the largest set of secretarial files in the collection.
    - R.I., 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Committees, 1971-1973 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - New members, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Other Clubs, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Secretary, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Treasurer, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - President, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Bulletin, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Program Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Classification Comm., 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Student Exchange, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Other Clubs, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Attendance Comm., 1972 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Public Relations Comm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Community Service Comm., 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Misc. Comms., 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - District Governor, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Rotary International, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Rotary Foundation, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - District Governor, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Radio Week, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Student Exchange, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Rotary Internat, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Rotary Foundation, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Attendance, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Community Service, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Public Address, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Misc., 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 28)
      Committee documents
    - Other Clubs, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Board of Directors, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Classification, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Program, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 32)
      Programming Committee
    - Bulletin, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - President, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Secretary, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Treasurer, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Secretary, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Treasurer, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - President, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Classification, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Club Service, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Community Service, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Fellowship, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Interact--Diplomats, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Misc., 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      Club social activities and committees
    - Orientation, 1973-1975 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Program, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Public Address, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Student Exchange, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - District 717, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Rotary International, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Rotary Foundation, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Other Clubs, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Leaves of Absence, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Board of Directors, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Roster, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Secretary, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Treasurer, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - President, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Attendance, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Board of Dir., 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Bulletin, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Classification, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Club Service, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Community Service, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Interact--Diplomats, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Leaves of Absence, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Misc., 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Orientation, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Other Clubs, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Student Exchange, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Program, 1973-1976 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Youth, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - District 717, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Rotary International, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Rotary Foundation, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Secretary, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Treasurer, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - President, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Board of Direct., 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Bulletin, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Classification, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Club Service, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Community Service, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Interact--Diplomat, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Leave of Absence, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Misc., 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Other Clubs, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Program, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Public Relations, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Roster, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Student Exch., 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - District 717, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Rotary Foundation, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Rotary International, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Youth, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Secretary, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Treasurer, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - President, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Board of Directors, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Bulletin, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Classification, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Club Service, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Community Service, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Fellowship, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Interact, 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Leaves of Absence, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Misc., 1977 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Other Clubs, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Program, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Public Relations, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Student Exchange, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Rotary Foundation, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - District 717, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Rotary Internat., 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Secretary, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Treasurer, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - President, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Board of Directors, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Bulletin--The News, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Classification, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Club Service, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Community Service, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Fellowship, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Leaves of Absence, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Other Clubs, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Pancake Day, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Pancake Day, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Pancake Day, 1975-2003 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Program, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Public Relations, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Student Exchange, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - District 717, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Rotary Foundation, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Rotary International, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Bob Head's Secretary's Notebook, 1971-1979 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Bob Head's Secretary's Notebook, 1974-1979 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Bob Head's Secretary's Notebook, 1976-1979 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Bob Head's Secretary's Notebook, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Series V. Districts
  Ithaca Rotary has been part of various Rotary districts since its foundation. These files include material from Districts 187, 253, 254, 717 and 7170. Material includes Ithaca Rotary Annual Club Assembly reports to the district, district newsletters, district conference materials and correspondence.
  - Newsletter, District 187, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - District 253 Map, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Annual Club Assembly (Dist. 254), 1955 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Annual Club Assembly (Dist. 717), 1961 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Annual Club Assembly (Dist. 717), 1962 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Annual Club Assembly (Dist. 717), 1966 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - District 717 Conferences, 1962-1974 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - District 717 Conferences, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Dist 717, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - District Governor, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - District 717 Conference, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Misc. District 717, 1973-1976 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Dist. 717, John Seeley, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Dist. 717 Conference and Directory, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Dist. 717 Paul Harris Fellows Programs, 1983-1986 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Ithaca Rotary Hosts Dist. 7170 Conference, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Dist. Assembly (7170), 2001 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - District Conference (7170), 2015 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Directories and newsletters (7170), 2009-2014 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    -newsletters are on a CD [CD-2220]
  - Additional loose directories, ca. 1982-2003 (Box 33)
  - District 7170 conference, 2015-2016 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Ithaca Rotary Club District - Pass the Gavel, 2012 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Rotary District Simplified Grant, 2012 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Series VI. Rotary Foundation
  Material related to the Ithaca Rotary Club’s fundraising for the Rotary Foundation, and to programs sponsored through the Foundation, including the Group Study Exchange. Includes correspondence, certificates, publications and reports.
  - R.F. Fellowship Applications, 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - R.F. Certificates, 1960-1980 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - R.F. Misc. Correspondence, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - R.F. Audit Report, 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - R.F. Notebook, 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Rotary Foundation, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Rotary Foundation Fellowship, 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Rotary Foundation Letters, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - R.F. Group Study Exchange (Japan), 1970 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Rotary Foundation Receipts, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - R.F. and District (John Seeley), 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    Includes a note written in 1995, explaining the materials
  - Rotary Fdn., 1977 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Rotary Fdn., 1978 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - R.F. Drive, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - General Publications, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Paul Harris Fellows (Whalen), 1987 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - R.F. Matching Grant (Egypt), 2001 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - R.F. Matching Grant (Kenya), 2001 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - R.F. Group Study Exchange Application, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - R.F. Giving Report, 2005-2006 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Rotary Foundation Certificates, 2006-2008 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - R.F. Group Study Exchange, 1983-1990 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Rose sale fundraiser history, ca. 1998-2008 (Box 33, Folder 4-7)
  - Foundation Dinner, 2015 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Series VII. Ithaca Rotary Club Publications
  Includes the weekly Ithaca Rotary Club publication, entitled THE ROTARY CLUB NEWS. Later issues carry the title of THE NEWS, but all issues of the publication are bound together in the collection under the title THE ROTARY CLUB NEWS. The collection includes both bound and loose issues, along with other Ithaca Rotary pamphlets and publications.
  - Rotary Club News and The News (Unbound), 1935-1965 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - The News (Unbound), 1964-1965 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - The News (Unbound), 1968 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - The News (Unbound), 1969 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - The News (Unbound), 1970 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - The News (Unbound), 1971 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - The News (Unbound), 1972 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - The News (Unbound), 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - The News (Unbound), 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - The News (Unbound), 1977-1978 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - The News (Unbound), 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - The News and Rotary Club News (Unbound)--Misc., 1944-1951 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    Loose supplements and issues
  - Drafts, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - The News, 1994-2007 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Ithaca Rotary Publications, 1954-1995 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 19, 1933-1934 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 20, 1934-1935 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 21, 1935-1936 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 22, 1936-1937 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 23, 1937-1938 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 24, 1938-1939 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 25, 1939-1940 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 26, 1940-1941 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 27, 1941-1942 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 28, 1942-1943 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 29, 1943-1944 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 30, 1944-1945 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 31, 1945-1946 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 32, 1946-1947 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 33, 1947-1948 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 34, 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 34-35, 1949-1950 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 36, 1950-1951 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 37-38, 1952-1953 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 39, 1953-1954 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 40, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 41, 1955-1956 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 41, 1956-1967 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    Labeled as Vol. 41, but also includes the first part of 42
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 43, 1967-1958 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    Labeled as Vol. 43, but also includes the second part of 42
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 45, 1959-1960 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 46, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 47, 1961-1962 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol.48, 1962-1963 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 49, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 50, 1964-1965 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 50, 1964-1965 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 51, 1965-1966 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 51, 1965-1966 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 52, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 52, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 53, 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 53, 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 54, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 54, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 55, 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 56, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 57, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 58, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 59, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 60, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 61, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 62, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 63, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 64, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 65, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 66, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 67, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 68, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 69, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 70, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 71, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 72, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 73, 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 74, 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 74, 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 75, 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 76, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 77, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 78, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 78, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 79, 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 80, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 81, 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 82, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 83, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 84, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 86, 1999-2000 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 87, 2000-2001 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 88, 2001-2002 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 89, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Rotary Club News, Vol. 89, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - eBulletins, 2013-2014 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Little Apple Fall Follies (LAFF), 2015-2016 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Little Apple Fall Follies (LAFF), 2017-10 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Brochures/pamphlets, 2015-2016 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Brochures/pamphlets (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - eBulletins, 2008-2009 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - eBulletins, 2009-2010 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - eBulletins, 2010-2011 (Box 36, Folder 27)
- Series VIII. Rotary International
  Rotary International publications, including conference proceedings. Also includes Ithaca Rotary Club files related to both Rotary International and to fellow Rotary clubs.
  - General
    - Misc Other Clubs, 1955-1973 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Nearby Clubs, 1957-1999 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - R.I. Semi-annual Report Materials, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Rotarian Mailing List, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Fukuoka Rotary Club--Cornell Glee Club, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Bulletins from Other Clubs, 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Ithaca-Cayuga Rotary Club, 1971-1978 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - R.I. Convention, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Misc Other Clubs, 1972-1980 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Dryden Rotary (Ithaca Sponsorship), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Planning guide, 2005-5008 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Rotary International packet, 2010 (Box 39)
  - Publications
    - Convention Proceedings, 1918 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1919 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1920 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1921 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1922 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1923 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1924 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1925 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1926 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1927 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1929 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1930 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1931 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1932 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1936 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1938 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1939 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1941 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1944 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1945 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1946 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1947 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1948 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1951 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 9)